{"login":{"title":"Login","messageUnauth":"Wrong email or password","messageSuspended":"Your account is suspended","messageInactive":"Your account is inactive","form":{"email":{"placeholder":"Email","error_required":"Email is required","error_wrong_email_format":"Wrong email format"},"password":{"placeholder":"Password","error_required":"Password is required"},"submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset"},"preferredLanguage":"Preferred language"},"shared":{"brand":"Triage Portal","nav":{"triageChoice":"Triage choice","results":"Results","logout":"Logout","login":"Login","howToTest":"How to test","tests":"Tests"},"contactus":"Contact us","submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset","ok":"Ok","cancel":"Cancel"},"modal":{"headerSorry":"Sorry","messageTryLater":"Something went wrong, please try again later."},"triageChoice":{"title":"Triages at your service","triages":[{"id":1,"name":"ACSS","link":"acss","description":"I am a very simple card. I am good at containing small bits of information. I am convenient because I require little markup to use effectively."},{"id":2,"name":"PM Ejacul","link":"pe","description":"I am a very simple card. I am good at containing small bits of information. I am convenient because I require little markup to use effectively."}],"walkIn":"Walk-in","remote":"Remote","results":"Results"},"contactus":{"title":"Contact us","form":{"yourName":{"placeholder":"Your name","error_required":"Name required"},"email":{"placeholder":"Email","error_required":"Email required","error_wrong_email_format":"Wrong email format"},"reason":{"placeholder":"Reason","error_required":"Reason required"},"message":{"placeholder":"Message","error_required":"Message required"},"bestContact":{"placeholder":"Best way to conatct you"},"submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset"}},"patient":{"title":"Patient data","form":{"firstname":{"placeholder":"First name","error_required":"First name required"},"lastname":{"placeholder":"Last name","error_required":"Last name required"},"email":{"placeholder":"Email","error_required":"Email required","error_wrong_email_format":"Wrong email format"},"dateOfBirth":{"placeholder":"Date of birth","error_required":"Date of birth required"},"visitType":{"placeholder":"Visit type","error_required":"Visit type required","initial":"Initial visit","followUp":"Follow up visit"},"race":{"placeholder":"Race","native":"American Indian or Alaska Native","african":"African American","asian":"Asian","caucasian":"Caucasian","islander":"Native Hawaiian or Other Pacific Islander"},"created_at":"Created at","created_by":"Created by","submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset","search":"Search","startTriage":"Start triage"},"noResultsFound":"No results found","emailInUse":"The email has already been taken","registerNewPatient":"Register new patient","datePicker":{"defaultDate":"2020-03-02T05:00:00.000Z","maxDate":"2021-01-31T05:00:00.000Z","yearRange":[1920,2020]},"remote":{"title":"Remote patient","message":"Triage link has been sent to","message1":"Link is expired or corrupt","message2":"Please contact your provider for new link","preferredLanguage":"Preferred language"}},"results":{"title":"Results:","doctor":"Doctor:","date":"Date:","triage":"Triage:","patient":"Patient:","visit":"Visit:","result":"Result:","suggestions":"Suggestions","initial":"Initial","followUp":"Follow Up","suggs":["Lorem ipsum dolor, sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit.","Optio, voluptatum explicabo aperiam a consequuntur aliquid quos sapiente fugiat suscipit modi eveniet et pariatur.","Commodi praesentium harum esse voluptas asperiores suscipit."],"print":"Print","savePdf":"Save PDF","remote1":"Your answers have been submitted","remote2":"Your health provider will contact you","header":"Traige Portal","pdfTitle":"Triage result"},"staff":{"title":"Staff manager","title2":"Add/Edit user","title3":"User setup","staffName":"Staff name","search":"Search","submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset","noResultsFound":"No user found","emailInUse":"The email has already been taken","linkExpired":"Link is expired or corrupt","preferredLanguage":"Preferred language","form":{"firstname":{"placeholder":"First name","error_required":"First name is required"},"lastname":{"placeholder":"Last name","error_required":"Last name is required"},"position":{"placeholder":"Position","error_required":"Position is required"},"email":{"placeholder":"Email","error_required":"Email is required","error_wrong_email_format":"Wrong email format"},"accessType":{"placeholder":"Access type","error_required":"Access type is required","regular":"Regular","manager":"Manager","superuser":"Superuser"},"password":{"placeholder":"Password","error_required":"Password is required","error_minLength":"Minimum length of password is 8","error_pattern":"Password should contain at least one digit and special character"},"passwordConfirm":{"placeholder":"Confirmation password","error_required":"Confirmation password is required","error_passwordMismatch":"Passwords didn't match"},"save":"Save","cancel":"Cancel","submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset"},"modal":{"successText":"User has been added successfully","modalHeader":"Staff manager"},"ok":"Ok"},"acss":{"title":"ACSS","patient":"Patient","patientName":"Patient name","visitType":"Visit type","initial":"Initial","followUp":"Folow up","form":{"typical":{"name":"Typical","instructions":"Please indicate whether you have had the following symptoms during the past 24 hours, and how severe they were","qs":[{"id":"1","question":"Frequent urination of small amounts of urine (going to the toilet very often)","description":"(going to the toilet very often)","answer":{"none":"None (up to 4 times/day)","mild":"Yes, mild (5-6 times/day)","moderate":"Yes, moderate (7-8 times/day)","severe":"Yes, severe (9-10 or more times/day)"}},{"id":"2","question":"Urgent urination (a sudden and uncontrollable urge to urinate)","description":"(a sudden and uncontrollable urge to urinate)","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}},{"id":"3","question":"Feeling burning pain when urinating","description":"","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}},{"id":"4","question":"Feeling incomplete bladder emptying (still feel like you could urinate again after urination)","description":"(still feel like you could urinate again after urination)","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}},{"id":"5","question":"Feeling pain not associated with urination in the lower abdomen (below the belly button)","description":"(below the belly button)","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}},{"id":"6","question":"Blood seen in urine (without menses)","description":"(without menses)","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}}]},"differential":{"name":"Differential","qs":[{"id":"7","question":"Flank pain (pain in one or both sides of the lower back)","description":"(pain in one or both sides of the lower back)","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}},{"id":"8","question":"Abnormal vaginal discharge (amount, color and/or odor)","description":"(amount, color and/or odor)","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}},{"id":"9","question":"Discharge from the urethra (urinary opening) , without urination","description":"(urinary opening) , without urination","answer":{"none":"None","mild":"Yes, mild","moderate":"Yes, moderate","severe":"Yes, severe"}},{"id":"10","question":"Fever/high body temperature (Please indicate if measured)","description":" (Please indicate if measured)","answer":{"none":"None (≤99.5°F)","mild":"Yes, mild (99.6°F-100.2°F)","moderate":"Yes, moderate (100.3°F-102.0°F)","severe":"Yes, severe (≥102.1 °F)"}}]},"qualityOfLife":{"name":"Quality of life","qs":[{"id":"11","question":"Please indicate how much discomfort you have experienced because of your symptoms in the past 24 hours (Mark answer that suits you best)","description":"(Mark answer that suits you best)","answer":{"none":"Feeling no discomfort (No symptoms at all. I feel as good as usual)","mild":"Feeling mild discomfort (I feel a somewhat worse than usual)","moderate":"Feeling moderate discomfort (I feel quite bad)","severe":"Feeling severe discomfort (I feel terrible)"}},{"id":"12","question":"Please indicate how your symptoms have interfered with your everyday activities/work in the past 24 hours (Mark answer that suits you best)","description":" (Mark answer that suits you best)","answer":{"none":"Not interfered at all (Working as usual on a working day)","mild":"Mildly interfered (Working is associated with some discomfort)","moderate":"Moderately interfered (Daily work requires effort)","severe":"Severely interfered (Usual work or activities are almost impossible)"}},{"id":"13","question":"Please indicate how your symptoms have interfered with your social activities (visiting people, meeting with friends, etc) in the past 24 hours (Mark answer that suits you best)","description":"(Mark answer that suits you best)","answer":{"none":"Not interfered at all (Working as usual on a working day)","mild":"Mildly interfered (Working is associated with some discomfort)","moderate":"Moderately interfered (Daily work requires effort)","severe":"Severely interfered (Usual work or activities are almost impossible)"}}]},"additional":{"name":"Additional","instructions":"Please indicate whether you have the followings today","qs":[{"id":"14","question":"Menstruation (Menses)","description":"(Menses)","answer":{"no":"No","yes":"Yes"}},{"id":"15","question":"Premenstrual syndrome (PMS)","description":"(PMS)","answer":{"no":"No","yes":"Yes"}},{"id":"16","question":"Signs of menopausal syndrome (e.g. hot flashes)","description":"(e.g. hot flashes)","answer":{"no":"No","yes":"Yes"}},{"id":"17","question":"Pregnancy","description":"","answer":{"no":"No","yes":"Yes"}},{"id":"18","question":"Known (diagnosed) diabetes mellitus (high sugar level)","description":"(high sugar level)","answer":{"no":"No","yes":"Yes"}}]},"dynamics":{"name":"Dynamics","qs":[{"id":"19","question":"Please indicate if you experienced any changes in your symptoms since the first time you completed this questionnaire:","description":"","answer":{"normal":"Yes I feel normal (All symptoms have gone away)","better":"Yes, I feel much better (Most of symptoms have gone away)","somebetter":"Yes, I feel somewhat better (Only some symptoms are gone)","barely":"No, there are barely any changes (I still have about the same symptoms)","worse":"Yes, I feel worse (My condition is worse)"}}]},"chooseAnswer":"Choose your answer","submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset"}},"pe":{"title":"Premature Ejaculation","patient":"Patient","patientName":"Patient name","visitType":"Visit type","initial":"Initial","followUp":"Folow up","form":{"ejacul":[{"id":"1","question":"Rate in scores how difficult  for you hold up (control) offensive of  ejaculation?","answerA":"Easy, can control","answerB":"Can be a little difficult","answerC":"Difficult","answerD":"Very hard","answerE":"Impossible"},{"id":"2","question":"How often your ejaculation occurs earlier than desired moment?","answerA":"Almost never or rarely","answerB":"Less than half of  the cases","answerC":"About half the cases","answerD":"More than half of the cases","answerE":"Almost always or always"},{"id":"3","question":"How often do you have premature ejaculation (at the very beginning of vaginal penetration)?","answerA":"Almost never or rarely","answerB":"Less than half of  the cases","answerC":"About half the cases","answerD":"More than half of the cases","answerE":"Almost always or always"},{"id":"4","question":"Duration of sexual intercourse (from penetration until ejaculation)?","answerA":"7-14 minutes and more","answerB":"From 3 to 6 minutes","answerC":"From 1 to 2 minutes","answerD":"Less than 1 minute","answerE":"30 seconds"},{"id":"5","question":"Does premature ejaculation occur only when you change your partner?","answerA":"Ocurs very rarely, and only when I change partner, it is OK with constant","answerB":"Sometimes occurs when I change the partner","answerC":"Half of the cases when you change partner","answerD":"More than half of cases when you change partner","answerE":"No, not only, occurs even with a constant partner"},{"id":"6","question":"Do you think that your partner is satisfied with sexual life?","answerA":"Yes, quite","answerB":"More \"yes\" than \"no\"","answerC":"About half the cases","answerD":"More \"no\" than \"yes\"","answerE":"No"},{"id":"7","question":"Do you have before or during intercourse, anxiety, restlessness?","answerA":"No (never)","answerB":"Rarely insignificantly","answerC":"Sometimes, but not always","answerD":"Very often","answerE":"Always"},{"id":"8","question":"Does it bother you that ejaculation occur faster than you would like?","answerA":"No (never)","answerB":"Rarely insignificantly","answerC":"Sometimes, but not always","answerD":"Very often","answerE":"Always"}],"controlQA":{"id":"9","question":"Have you experienced early ejaculation from the very first days of your sexual life?","answerA":"Yes","answerB":"No"},"chooseAnswer":"Choose your answer","submit":"Submit","reset":"Reset"}}}